import {IQuestion} from "@/store/questions/questions.types";

export const easyCurrenciesData: IQuestion[] = [
    {
            question: 'Where USD is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'United States'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where CZK is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Czech Republic'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where GBP is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'United Kingdom'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where JPY is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Japan'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where UAH is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Ukraine'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where CNY is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'China'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where INR is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'India'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where BRL is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Brazil'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where AUD is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Australia'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where CAD is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Canada'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where ZAR is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'South Africa'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where MXN is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Mexico'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where ARS is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Argentina'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where CLP is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Chile'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where EGP is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Egypt'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where NGN is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Nigeria'
        },
        {
            question: 'Where GHS is main currency?',
            correct_answer: 'Ghana'
        }
    ]